https://www.mecvel.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Company information Company Name: MECVEL S.r.l.Registered Office Address: Via Due Portoni 23, 40132, Bologna, ItalyVAT Number: 04313760375Fiscal Code: 03717630374Business Reg. Office: BOSubscription No. Business Reg.: 311496Capital: € 119.600 i.v.Single-member Company: NoCompany in Liquidation: No This page describes the management mode of the site with reference to personal data processing of users consulting it.This is an information for those who interact with the web services of MECVEL S.r.l. company, available on www.mecvel.com.The processing of personal data provided and or deduced browsing the site is undergone with these purposes:To allow the access and the browsing of the site (service execution)To process anonymous statistics on the use of the site (legitimate interest)To check the correct functioning status of the site and identify any responsibility in case of unlawful acts during the browsing (legitimate interest)Informatics’ systems and software procedures used for the correct working of the site collect, during their functioning, some personal data whose transmission is included in the use of Internet communication protocols: accessing the site leads the company to get these data.In general, we inform you that your personal data processing will be done with electronic devices and could consist in their collection, registration, storage, modification, communication, cancellation.All personal data processed by MECVEL S.r.l. are protected by appropriate security measures, according to the current legislation and for the time strictly necessary to fulfill purposes (one year for site’s visitors).Personal data collected in accordance with what is mentioned above will not be communicated or disclosed to third parts, unless requested by judicial authorities.According to the art. 13 of RGPD (EU) 2016/679, we remind that you have the right to request to MECVEL S.r.l. the access to your personal data, their correction, cancellation (where applicable) or limitation of processing.It also has the right to revoke the authorization to data processing for which the consent has been given, as well as the right to submit a complaint to the Personal Data Protection Authority.All the rights mentioned above can be exercised writing to info@mecvel.com.We will reply you as soon as possible.Cookies processing informationYour PrivacyMECVEL S.r.l. is involved in protecting your personal data and this document has the task to help you in understanding which information we could collect about you and how we could use them.What are cookies and how we use them?A cookie is a simple text file stored on your computer or mobile device from the server of the site, and only that server will be able to retrieve or read its content.It contains some anonymous information and allows the site to remember some data.There are different kinds of cookies, which can be defined as follow:TECHNICAL COOKIESNavigation or session cookies: used only with the purpose of transmitting a communication on an electronic communications network, or needed to provide the service required by the userAnalytics: used to collect information on the number of users and on how they browse the site (if used directly by the site handler)Functionality cookies: they allow the user to browse the site according to a series of selected criteria (for example the language), with the aim to improve the servicePROFILING COOKIES: dedicated to create user profiles and used in order to send advertising messages in accordance with preferences shown by the user while browsing the netWhy we use cookies?MECVEL S.r.l. uses cookies to allow its systems to recognize your device and offer you some functionalities, including facilitating the navigation of the site and its proper use, facilitating access to services that require an authentication, and to know which areas of the site have been visited. Cookies used in the site are both persistent (they remain stored until they expiration on the hard disk of the user’s computer) and session cookies (they are not stored permanently on the user’s computer and disappear closing the browser).The company uses cookies also for other reasons as:Identify the user in the moment of accessing the site: in this way the company can provide recommendations on products, show personalized content, make available other functions and customized servicesBe aware of documents downloaded from www.mecvel.comThis is the list of cookies used in this site:ASPSESSIONID Purpose: It allows to recognize the user's browsing sessionKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: End of the sessionSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Session ID (the cookie name changes in each session)Cases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.STATO_CLI_FORPurpose: It allows to profile the client during the navigationKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Customer statusCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.DescrizionePurpose: Customer/Company nameKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Customer/Company nameCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.AmbitoPurpose: Navigation data related to the domainKind of cookies: Functional cookiesDuration: End of the sessionSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Navigation data related to the domain (Language, Scope and Country)Cases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.CheckPurpose: Customer CodeKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Customer CodeCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.ClientePurpose: Customer’s dataKind of cookies: Functional cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Nation, Sales, PowerUse role definitionCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.AntcliPurpose: Customer sales channelKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Customer sales channelCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.PilotPurpose: Navigation condition on site prototypeKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: End of the sessionSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: It indicates if the customer is enabled for new features of the site (through a check of the customer code)Cases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.CodUtentePurpose: Navigation userKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Customer contactCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.idLinguaPurpose: Navigation languageKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: End of the sessionSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Navigation languageCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmx, __utmxx, __utmz, _gaPurpose: It allows to analyze the use of the site by users, to improve content and servicesKind of cookies: Analytical cookiesDuration: __utma 2 years, __utmb 1 hour, __utmc end of the session, _utmz 6 months, _ga 2 yearsSource and property of cookies: Google AnalyticsRegistered information: Browsing data, as visited pages, IP address, user's originCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: For information on Google Analytics cookies read here, while for information on Google Inc. privacy policy read hereAltroPurpose: Navigation data related to the domainKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: End of the sessionSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Navigation dataCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.XnetPurpose: Authentication to domainKind of cookies: Technical cookiesDuration: 1 daySource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Authentication to domainCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.cookiePrivacyPurpose: it reminds if the user has already seen and accepted cookies privacy conditionsKind of cookies: Functional cookiesDuration: 1 monthSource and property of cookies: www.mecvel.comRegistered information: Expiry dateCases in which it is used: The whole siteAccess to information: MECVEL S.r.l.How to control cookies?The "Guide" section of your browser should be able to help you with the management of your cookie settings.If you do not want to receive cookies, you can change your browser settings to notify you when they are sent.It is also possible to delete cookies that have already been stored at any time, using the browser settings.It is possible to choose if accept or not cookies set by our site in the cookies settings page.Cookies must be accepted to visit the site? No, it is not mandatory.It is possible to disable them simply deactivating the cookies function in your browser.However, some parts of the site, as well as other web pages, could not work correctly once the function is disabled.For example, in case of access to the restricted area, the site cannot proceed without the authentication provided by cookies.
© 2020 MecVel srl - P. IVA 04313760375
Privacy policy
Sale conditions
We are hiring
About us
Scroll
MecVel uses cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this website, you agree with our use of cookies. If you want more information: Read More Accept
